Guide to the Adler hip hop archive, circa 1970-2013.
Adler hip hop archive
- Series I. News Files
  - News Files 1990s and 2000s
    - Performer Names Q-Z
      - Spearhead
        - Spearhead photos, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 35)
        - Spearhead '95, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 36)
        - Spearhead press materials etc, 1994-1995 (Box 27, Folder 37)
        - Spearhead U.K., Canadian etc press, 1994-1995 (Box 27, Folder 38)
        - Spearhead '96-'06, 1996-2006 (Box 27, Folder 39)
        - Spearhead lyrics, No Date (Box 27, Folder 40)
      - Spice-1, 1993-2007 (Box 27, Folder 41)
      - Sporty Thievz, No Date (Box 27, Folder 42)
      - Lawrence Stanley, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 43)
      - Star and Buc Wild, 2000-2006 (Box 27, Folder 44)
      - State Property, c. 2002 (Box 27, Folder 45)
      - Karrine Steffans, 2005 (Box 27, Folder 46)
      - Steph Lova, 2001-2002 (Box 27, Folder 47)
      - Stereo MCs
        - Stereo MCs press, 1990-2001 (Box 27, Folder 48)
        - Stereo MCs bios, labels, etc, 1990-1991, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 49)
        - Stereo MCs photos, c. 2001, No Date (Box 27, Folder 50)
      - Sticky Fingaz, 2001-2003 (Box 27, Folder 51)
      - Stimulated Dummies, 1993-2001 (Box 27, Folder 52)
      - Angie Stone, 2000-2001 (Box 27, Folder 53)
      - Scott Storch, 2005 (Box 27, Folder 54)
      - Steve Stoute, 2001-2012 (Box 27, Folder 55)
      - Adario Strange, 1993-2004 (Box 27, Folder 56)
      - The Streets, 2008 (Box 27, Folder 57)
      - Styles P a/k/a Styles, 2001-2007 (Box 27, Folder 58)
      - Success-N-Effect, 1990-1992 (Box 27, Folder 59)
      - Suede, 2004 (Box 27, Folder 60)
      - Super Cat, 1995 (Box 27, Folder 61)
      - Supernatural, 1994-1999 (Box 27, Folder 62)
      - Sway and Tech a/k/a Sway and King Tech, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 63)
      - Swizz Beatz, 1999-2012 (Box 27, Folder 64)
      - Tairrie B, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 65)
      - "Tales From the Hood" (soundtrack), 1995 (Box 27, Folder 66)
      - Tech N9ne, 2009-2012 (Box 27, Folder 67)
      - Terminator X, 1990-1994, 2013 (Box 27, Folder 68)
      - Terror Squad, 2004-2005 (Box 27, Folder 69)
      - "Thicker Than Water" (movie with Mack 10 and Fat Joe), 1999 (Box 27, Folder 70)
      - Three 6 Mafia, 1998-2006 (Box 27, Folder 71)
      - Thug Life, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - T.I., 2004-2013 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Timbaland, 1997-2013 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Tim Dog, 1991-2012 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Toddy Tee, 1995, 2007 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Gabe Tolliver, 2004-2007 (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Tone Loc, 1989-1996 (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - Tony D, 1990-1992, 2009 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - Tony Touch, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 9)
      - David Toop, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 10)
      - Top Quality, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 11)
      - Toure, 1998-2013 (Box 28, Folder 12)
      - T-Pain, 2007-2011 (Box 28, Folder 13)
      - "Training Day" (movie), 2001 (Box 28, Folder 14)
      - Obie Trice, 2003-2006 (Box 28, Folder 15)
      - Trick Daddy, 1997-2005 (Box 28, Folder 16)
      - Trill (record label), 2006-2010 (Box 28, Folder 17)
      - Trillville, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 18)
      - Trina, 2000-2012 (Box 28, Folder 19)
      - Troubleneck Brothers, 1993-1994 (Box 28, Folder 20)
      - The Tunnel (nightclub), 1989, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 21)
      - Tupac, a/k/a Tupac Shakur and 2Pac
        - Tupac '91-'93, 1991-1993 (Box 28, Folder 22)
        - Tupac's music as a factor in Austin, Tx., murder trial, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 23)
        - Bill Adler editorial re Dan Quayle versus Tupac, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 24)
        - Tupac '94, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 25)
        - Tupac '95-96, 1995-1996 (Box 28, Folder 26)
        - Tupac's death, 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 27)
        - John Singleton, Jasmine Guy re Tupac, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 28)
        - Tupac, the after-life, 1996-2006, 1996-2013 (Box 28, Folder 29)
        - Tupac articles by Chuck Phillips, 2002-2012 (Box 28, Folder 30)
        - Confession by Dexter Isaac in the 1994 shooting of Tupac Shakur, 2011 (Box 28, Folder 31)
      - Tweet, 2002-2005 (Box 28, Folder 32)
      - Twinz, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 33)
      - Twista, 1994-2007 (Box 28, Folder 34)
      - Tyga, 2012-2013 (Box 28, Folder 35)
      - Us3, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 36)
      - UGK, including Bun B and Pimp C, 2001-2013 (Box 28, Folder 37)
      - Vanilla Ice, 1990-2012 (Box 28, Folder 38)
      - Vanity Fair, 2005 (Box 28, Folder 39)
      - Vibe (magazine), 1992-2013 (Box 28, Folder 40)
      - VP Records, 2002 (2013) (Box 28, Folder 41)
      - "The Wackness" (movie), 2008 (Box 28, Folder 42)
      - Waka Flocka Flame, 2012 (Box 28, Folder 43)
      - Paul Wall, 2005-2006 (Box 28, Folder 44)
      - Warren G, 1994-2002 (Box 28, Folder 45)
      - Wax Poetics (magazine), including Andre Torres, 2011 (Box 28, Folder 46)
      - WC and the Maad Circle, c. 1995 (Box 28, Folder 47)
      - Webbie, 2008 (Box 28, Folder 48)
      - Cornel West, 2001-2007 (Box 28, Folder 49)
      - Kanye West
        - Kanye West '00-'09, 2004-2009 (Box 28, Folder 50)
        - Kanye West '10-'13, 2010-2013 (Box 28, Folder 51)
      - Westside Connection, c. 1997 (Box 28, Folder 52)
      - Armond White, 1993-2000, 2010 (Box 28, Folder 53)
      - "Whiteboys" (movie), 1999 (Box 28, Folder 54)
      - Wild Pitch (record label), 2001 (Box 28, Folder 55)
      - Hype Williams, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 56)
      - Wendy Williams, 1999-2009 (Box 28, Folder 57)
      - Willie D, 1992-2007 (Box 28, Folder 58)
      - Elliot Wilson, 2005 (Box 28, Folder 59)
      - Wiz Khalifa, 2011-2012 (Box 28, Folder 60)
      - Gail Woldu, 2006-2008 (Box 28, Folder 61)
      - Wreckx-n-Effect, 1989-1996 (Box 28, Folder 62)
      - Wu-Tang Clan, 1993-2013 (Box 28, Folder 63)
      - X-Clan, 1989-2008 (Box 28, Folder 64)
      - X-ecutioners, 1997-2008 (Box 28, Folder 65)
      - XXL (magazine), 1997 (Box 28, Folder 66)
      - Xzibit, 1996-2012 (Box 28, Folder 67)
      - Tony Yayo, 2005 (Box 28, Folder 68)
      - Yelawolf, 2010 (Box 28, Folder 69)
      - Ying Yang Twins, 2005-2006 (Box 28, Folder 70)
      - Yo Gotti, 2006-2007 (Box 28, Folder 71)
      - Yomo and Maulkie, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 72)
      - Yo-Yo, 1991-1998 (Box 28, Folder 73)
      - Young Bleed, 2007 (Box 28, Folder 74)
      - Young Buck, 2004-2008 (Box 28, Folder 75)
      - Young Capone, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 76)
      - Young Dro, 2006-2009 (Box 28, Folder 77)
      - Young Jeezy, 2005-2012 (Box 28, Folder 78)
      - Young MC, 1990 (Box 28, Folder 79)
      - Young Thug, 2013 (Box 28, Folder 80)
      - Yukmouth, c. 2004 (Box 28, Folder 81)
      - Yung Berg, 2008 (Box 28, Folder 82)
      - Yung Joc, 2007 (Box 28, Folder 83)
      - YZ, 1991-1994 (Box 28, Folder 84)
      - Zion 1, 1999-2000 (Box 28, Folder 85)
      - Z - Ro, 2006-2007 (Box 28, Folder 86)
- Series II. Posters and Framed Items
  Items are arranged by size and listed by artist(s)/creator(s), if known.
  - D.J. Jazzy Jeff and the Fresh Prince, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Record Label: Jive Records
    Notes: Counter display for the singles "Girls Ain't Nothing But Trouble" and "Parents Just Don't Understand." 2 parts.
    Size: 13.5in. x 16.5in.
  - DMX, 2006 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Event / Title: Fear of the Dog Again
    Record Label: Sony Records
    Notes: 2 copies
    Size: 18in. x 13in.
  - The Funky 4+1, c. 1980 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Notes: Band poster with Sugar Hill Records
    Size: 13.5in. x 18in.
  - Gangstarr, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Event / Title: Moment of Truth
    Record Label: Virgin Records and EMI
    Notes: Record release poster in the form of a large sticker
    Size: 10in. x 12in.
  - Ghetto Red Hot, undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Event / Title: Step Into the Realm
    Record Label: Lock Down Recordings
    Notes: Record release poster.
    Size: 9in. x 12in.
  - Ghostface Killah featuring Raheem Devaughn, Fabolous, Lloyd, Estelle, John Legend, Ron Browz, Adrienne Bailon, and Shareefa, September 29, 2009 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Event / Title: Ghostdini: Wizard of Poetry
    Record Label: Def Jam Recordings
    Notes: Record release poster. 2 sided.
    Size: 11in x 17in.
  - LL Cool J, undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Notes: Mass market poster
    Size: 11in. x 14in.
  - Ludacris featuring Nate Dogg, Mystikal, Jagged Edge, Twista, Three 6 Mafia, Shawnna, I-20, Lil Fate and 4 Ize, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Event / Title: Word of Mouf
    Notes: Record release poster
    Size: 11in. x 17in.
  - Mims, 2009 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Event / Title: Guilt
    Record Label: Capitol Records
    Notes: Record release poster. 2 copies
    Size: 8.5in x 11in.
  - Mr. Cheeks, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Event / Title: Back Again!
    Record Label: Universal Records
    Notes: Record release poster. 2 copies. 2 sided.
  - Scarface featuring Jay-Z, NAS, Kelly Price, Faith Evans and Beanie Sigel, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Event / Title: The Fix
  - T-Pain featuring Akon, Ludacris, Chris Brown, Ciara, Lil Wayne, DJ Khaled, Kanye West, T.I., 2008 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Event / Title: Thr33 Ringz
    Record Label: Zomba Records and Jive Records
  - WC featuring Snoop Dogg and Nate Dogg, Ice Cube and MC Ren, undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
    Event / Title: Ghetto Heisman
  - Akon featuring Lil' Wayne and Young Jeezy, December 2, 2008 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Event / Title: Freedom
    Notes: Album cover promotional flats. 2 sided.
    Size: 12in. x 24in.
  - Ant Banks featuring Ice Cube, Too Short, Mack 10, E40, Spice 1, WC, J-Dubb, King T, K-Dee, MC Breed, Rappin' 4-Tay, CJ Mac, Bad-N-Fluenz, Audrian, and Allfrumtha i, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Event / Title: Big Thangs
    Record Label: Priority Records
    Size: 12.5in. x 12.5in.
  - Busta Rhymes featuring Ron Browz, Young Jeezy and Jadakiss, T-Pain, 2009 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Event / Title: Back on My B.S.
    Record Label: Universal Motown
  - Cam'ron, 2009 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Event / Title: Crime Pays
    Record Label: Diplomat Records and Asylum Records.
    Notes: Album cover promotional flats. 2 sided. 2 copies.
    Size: 12in. x 12in.
  - De La Soul, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Event / Title: Stakes is High
    Record Label: Tommy Boy Records
  - DJ Khaled featuring Akon, T.I., Rick Ross, Fat Joe, Birdman, and Lil Wayne, 2007 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Event / Title: We The Best
    Record Label: Cash Money
  - DMX, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Event / Title: And Then There was X
  - The Dream featuring Fabolous, December 11, 2007 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Event / Title: Love Hate
    Record Label: Radio Killa and Def Jam Recordings
  - Geto Boys, March 9, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Event / Title: Till Death Do Us Part
    Record Label: Rap-A-Lot Records
    Notes: Album cover promotional flats 2 sided
  - Gorilla Zoe, March 17, 2009 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Event / Title: Don't Feed the Animals
    Record Label: Bad Boy and Boy South Records
  - Mims, 2007 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Event / Title: Music is My Savior
    Notes: Album cover promotional flats.
    Size: 12in.x 12in.
  - Mims, 2009 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Record Label: American King Music and Capitol Records
    Size: 10in. x 10in.
  - The Infamous Mobb Deep, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Event / Title: The Infamous
    Record Label: Loud Records
    Notes: Album cover promotional flats. Large sticker.
  - The Infamous Mobb Deep, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Event / Title: Murda Musik
    Record Label: Loud Records and Columbia Records
  - Ms. Dynamite, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Event / Title: A Little Deeper
    Record Label: Interscope Records
    Notes: Album cover promotional flats. Double sided.
  - The Murderers, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Event / Title: Irv Gotti presents…The Murderers
    Notes: Album cover promotional flats. 2 sided. Also mentioned on the
    poster are other artists on the Murder Inc. label - Ja Rule, Black Child, Vita, Tah Murdah, Ronnie Bumbs.
  - Pitbull featuring Lloyd and Go Girl, 2007 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Event / Title: The Boatlift
    Record Label: TVT Records
  - Public Enemy, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Event / Title: "Black Steel in the Hour of Chaos" from the LP "It Takes a Nation of Millions to Hold Us Back."
  - Public Enemy, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Event / Title: He Got Game: The Father, the Son, and the Holy Game
  - Rick Ross featuring Jay-Z, R. Kelly, Lil' Wayne, Young Jeezy, Nelly, 2008 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Event / Title: Trilla
  - Terror Squad featuring Fat Joe, Big Pun, Cuban Link, Triple Seis, Armageddon, Prospect, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Event / Title: Terror Squad: The Album
    Record Label: Atlantic Records
  - Three 6 Mafia featuring Akon, Lyfe Jennings, Pimp C, Lil Wyte, Unk, Good Charlotte, Project Pat and Young D, undated (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Event / Title: Last 2 Walk
    Record Label: Hypnotize Minds and Columbia Records
    Notes: Album cover promotional flats, with postcard and ticket sized flyers. Double sided. 2 copies.
    Size: 12in. x 17.5in.
  - T Pain, 2008 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - WC featuring Snoop Dogg; Nate Dogg; Ice Cube; MC Ren; Case, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Wu-Tang Clan, 2001 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    Event / Title: Iron Flag
  - Laurie Anderson, Peter Holsapple, David Johanson, Mark Kostabi, Arto Lindsay, Daniel Ponce, Run-DMC Suzanne Vega and Frank Christian, January 15, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Event / Title: The ARChive of Contemporary Music Benefit
    Venue: Limelight (New York, NY)
    Notes: Event poster. Artwork by Kostabi
  - Beastie Boys, c. 1987 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Event / Title: License to Ill Tour in Japan - Volume 1 and 2
    Notes: 4 tour posters in the shape of an arrow. In Japanese.
    Size: approx. 10in. x 14in.
  - Big Fat Love with Mike D of the Beastie Boys; Law and Order, June 30, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Event / Title: Blasted on Bleeker
    Venue: CBGB (New York, NY)
    Notes: Concert poster
    Size: 14in. x 22in.
  - Buckshot and Smif N Wessun; Sean Price with Heltah Skeltah; Kidz in the Hall; Blue Scholars; Skyzoo; Marco Polo and Torae; Team Facelift; Da Beatminerz (DJ Evil Dee and Mister Walt); hosted by Angela Yee and J-Hatch, October 24, 2009 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Event / Title: Duck Down CMJ Showcase
    Venue: The Gramercy Theater, New York, NY
    Notes: Concert and record release poster for Sean Price: Kimbo Price - The Prelude to Mic Tyson (on reverse.) 3 copies.
  - Buddy Guy, Steel Pulse, Gil Scott-Heron, Devotchka, Corinne Bailey Rae, CeU, Nicholas Payton, Dead Prez. Dr. Lonnie Smith, Bonobo (Live), Pretty Lights, Bernard "Pretty" Purdie, Christian Scott, John Brown's Body, King Khan and the Shrines, B-Side Players, Omar Sosa's Afreecanos, Toubab Krews, April 11-24, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Event / Title: Soul'd Out Music Festival
    Venue: Roseland Theater, Jimmy Mak's, Aladdin, Doug Fir, Berbati's and Wonder Ballroom (Portland, OR)
    Notes: Concert poster.
    Size: 10.5in. x 16.5in.
  - Capone and Noreaga, Mobb Deep, Havnotz, On the One's and Two's, DJ Clue's Desert Storm and The Crowd Motivator DJ Awesome, February 6, 2003 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Event / Title: Celebrity Pre-All-star Party
    Venue: Frequency (Atlanta, GA)
    Notes: Event poster.
    Size: 13in. x 19in.
  - DEEJ Lil' R, DEEJ Silk, DEEJ Fabulous, MC Chaps Hit-Teck, Siut Maarten, March 25, 2011 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Event / Title: Ladies Night Special Benz-Punanny Edition
    Venue: At Heavens Night Club (Saint Maarten)
    Size: 12in. x 18in.
  - DJ J-Nice, Biz Markie, DJ Kid Capri, Frank Ski, DJ Clue, DJ S&S, DJ Trauma, May 24-28 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Event / Title: Urban Paradise
    Venue: Flamenco Resort and Hotel (Punta Cana, Domican Republic)
    Notes: Concert flyer.
    Size: 5.25in. x 13.25in.
  - Freaky Outy, Dr. Adam, and Colin Jones, April 30, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Event / Title: 90s Dance Party
    Venue: Holocene (Portland, OR)
    Notes: Concert poster. Uses the same image from the LL Cool J poster.
    Size: 10.75in. x 16.75in.
  - Insane Clowne Posse featuring Kottonmouth Kings, Coolio, Necro and Kittie, June 4, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Event / Title: Happy Daze Tour
    Venue: Portland Expo Center (Portland, OR)
    Notes: Tour poster (or tour advertisement)
  - Izolan, DJ Tony Mix, Marco, Barikad Crew, April 2, 2011 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Event / Title: La Soiree Zero Stress
    Venue: 123 Soleil (Sint Maarten)
    Notes: Event poster. In French.
    Size: 12.5in. x 17.5in.
  - Kool DJ Red Alert, July 2, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Venue: The Funk Hut, Big City (New York, NY)
  - MURS, Sick Jackson and Serge Severe, April 30, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Event / Title: Mike Thrasher Presents
    Venue: Hawthorne Theater (Portland, OR)
  - Nosaj Thing, Body language, High Highs, Yeasayer, Chris Douridas and Jason Eldridge, undated (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Event / Title: School Night! 3D After Party
    Venue: The Bowery Hotel (New York, NY)
    Notes: Event poster in 3D with glasses
  - Platinum Sounds Musical Mix featuring Jason Bien and B.B.C. Sounds, September 19, 2009 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Event / Title: Pork Dance
    Venue: Living Room
    Notes: Event postcard. Double sided
    Size: 5in. x 7in.
  - Rakim, June 12, 2013 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Event / Title: Reebok Classic Concert series
    Venue: Joe's Pub (New York, NY)
  - R.A. the Rugged Man, March 8, 2012 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Event / Title: Fire Your Boss
    Venue: Bowery Poetry Club (New York, NY)
  - Rev Shines, DJ Kez, Dundiggy. Hosted by Ronin Roc, May 13, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Event / Title: Madlib: The Bad Kid (DJ Set)
    Venue: Someday Lounge (Portland, OR)
    Size: 11in. x 16.75in.
  - Run-DMC and EPMD, April 2 - 3, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Venue: The Marquee
    Size: 10.5in. x 15.25in.
  - Sean Price, Boot Camp Click, Sadat X, Brand Nubian, FEDD HILL, Rack-LO, FI-LO, Thirstin Howl the 3rd, PF Cuttin of Blahzay Blahzay, March 28, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    Venue: Jerkys (Providence, RI)
  - A$AP Rocky, April 2013 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Event / Title: Interview Magazine (featured article)
    Notes: 11 pages of the article, "Golden Boy A$AP Rocky" by Alexander Wang
    Size: 10in. x 13in.
  - Beastie Boys, April 14, 2012 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Event / Title: 27th Annual Rock and Roll Hall of Fame Induction
    Notes: Page from Cleveland's "The Plain Dealer" newspaper
    Size: 12in. x 22in.
  - Beastie Boys - Guns N' Roses, Red Hot Chili Peppers, Freddie King, The Small Faces/Faces, Donovan, Laura Nyro, May 5, 2012 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Event / Title: Rock and Roll Hall of Fame Induction Ceremony
    Venue: Rock and Roll Hall of Fame (HBO)
    Notes: Full-page advertisement cut from the New York Times
    Size: 11.5in. x 20.75in.
  - Big Daddy Kane, 1989 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Event / Title: Strictly Hip-Hop magazine
    Notes: Cover and first page - showing article about the "Stop the Violence Movement".
    Size: 11in. x 15in.
  - Big Daddy Kane, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Event / Title: Taste of Chocolate
    Record Label: Cold Chillin' Records
    Notes: Advertisement for record release taken from an unknown magazine (reverse has advertisement for album by New Kids on the Block)
    Size: 11in. x 13.5in.
  - Kurtis Blow, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Event / Title: Rhyme and Reason
    Notes: Movie advertisement from unknown magazine. Kurtis Blow as Executive Producer.
  - Sean Combs (Puff Daddy), January 3, 2013 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Event / Title: Sean John Tailored
    Notes: New York Times advertisement for Sean John line of men's clothing.
  - Drake, Nicki Minaj, Jennifer Lopez and Queen Latifah, July 13, 2012 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Event / Title: Ice Age Continental Drift
    Notes: New York Times movie advertisement
    Size: 12in.x 22in.
  - Dr. Dre, January 7, 2013 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Event / Title: Beats by Dr. Dre and Chrysler Group
    Notes: New York Times advertisement for beats audio.
  - Dr. Dre and Jimmy Iovine, May 21, 2013 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Event / Title: University of Southern California Irvine and Young Academy for Arts, Technology, and the Business of Innovation
    Notes: New York Times advertisement for the USC program
  - Flavor Flav, Mike Ross, Ton Loc, Young MC, True Mathmatics, MC Shy D, Baby D, Rockwell, Anquette, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Event / Title: Organized Rhyme Magazine
    Notes: Black and white photographs
  - Funkmaster Flex, December 8-14, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Event / Title: Stir the Senses Tour
    Notes: Advertisement from Village Voice for a chance to win a Cadillac Escalade customized by Funkmaster Flex
    Size: 9.75in. x 13.25in.
  - Ice-T, Big Daddy Kane, The Juice Crew, Latifah, Original Concept, Tuff Crew, Rob Base, D.J. Eazy Rock, Super Lover Cee, Casanova Rud, Tone Loc and Young Mac, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Notes: Magazine Cover. Tone Loc and Young MC on reverse in advertisement for Delicious Vinyl.
  - Lil Jon and The East Side Boyz, December 12, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Event / Title: $2 Dollar Bill Concert Series
    Venue: MTV2
    Notes: Ad from Village Voice December 8-14, 2004
  - Lil' Kim, November 1999 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Event / Title: Interview Magazine
    Notes: 5 pages of an Interview Magazine article about Lil' Kim
  - Public Enemy, Rage Against the Machine, Wu-Tang Clan, Cypress Hill, Erykah Badu, Rakim, Mos Def, Talib Kweli and over 22 other performers, July 28-29, 2007 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Event / Title: Rock the Bells
    Venue: Randall's Island
    Notes: Advertisement from Village Voice May 2, 2007
    Size: 10.5in. x 13in.
  - Kimora Lee Simmons, 2004 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Event / Title: Baby Phat
    Notes: Advertisement for Baby Phat from unknown magazine.
    Size: 9.75in. x 12in.
  - Russell Simmons, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Event / Title: Arude Magazine
    Notes: Advertisement for article "Godfather of Hip Hop Russell Simmons" by Anicee Gaddis
    Size: 11in. x 15.5in.
  - Russell Simmons, 2010 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Event / Title: Running Russell Simmons
    Notes: Advertisement for the TV show from AM New York newspaper. 2 pages
    Size: 11in. x 12in.
  - Snoop Doggie Dogg, September 1993 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Event / Title: Vibe Magazine
    Notes: Vibe magazine cover story about Snoop Dogg.
  - Snoop Dogg, April 12, 2013 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Event / Title: Scary Move V
    Notes: New York Times movie advertisement.
  - 3-D, Le Juan Love, 2 Live Crew, MC Shy D, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Notes: Advertisement for Luke Skywalker Records, and 3-D on reverse
  - T La Rock and Jazzy Jay, May 17, 2013 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Event / Title: Program Your 808 Series
    Notes: From the newspaper The Daily Note: diagram for
    T La Rock and Jazzy Jay's "It's Yours" 1984. "Use the diagram above to program your Roland
    TR-808 drum machine, then sit back while memories of your favorite 808 beats from the
    past are brought back to life."
    Size: 14.75in. x 23in.
  - 2 Live Crew, Stetsasonic, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    Notes: Advertisement for 2 Live Crew and article about Stetsasonic on reverse.
  - Cey Adams, Chris Cycle, and Vivian Goldman, January 28, 2013 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Event / Title: "Flood the Art Market" auction
    Venue: Cristin Tierney Gallery (New York, NY)
    Notes: Adidas World Famous Supreme Team 1962. Designed by Cey Adams. Signed by Cey Adams, Chris Cycle and Vivian Goldman
  - Def Jam Recordings, undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Notes: Promotional folder. 6 copies
    Size: 18in. x 15in.
  - Bill Adler and Cey Adams, February 9, 2012 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Event / Title: Def Jam: The Last Great Record Label
    Venue: Stanford University, The Institute for Diversity in the Arts
    Notes: Book release event poster. 3 copies
  - Bill Adler and Cey Adams, October 26, 2011 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    Event / Title: Oral History Live!
    Venue: Experience Music Project (Seattle, WA.)
    Size: 11.75in. x 17.75in.